A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Publications, Working Files and Photographs FA1394
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Publications, Working Files and Photographs
1968-2001
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA1394
21.18 Cubic Feet 55 containers
Related Materials
Original photographs from the 1991 and 1992 Annual Reports can be found in Ford Foundation records, Multimedia Material, Accession 2017:067 Other Ford Foundation publications collections include: Ford Foundation records, Publications (FA767) Ford Foundation records, Publications (Non-Grant Related), Accessions 2017:079 and 2017:089 (FA1394) Ford Foundation records, Special Collections Publications (FA1395)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Series 1: Publications - Working Files was transferred to RAC in 2017 and 2018 by the Ford Foundation and ingested by RAC as Accessions 2017:079, 2017:089, 2018:059, and 2018:086. Series 2: Photographs was originally ingested by RAC as part of Accessions 2017:084 and 2018:089.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted (Boxes 21-24 contain confidental material). Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Materials are arranged into two series:
1. Publications - Working Files
2. Photographs
Scope and Contents
Ford Foundation records, Publications, Working Files and Photographs houses publication files of the Office of Communications' Art and Design Unit. Documents within the collection include proofs, correspondence, drafts, memoranda, licensing agreements, typesetting specifications, distribution files, photographs, and final versions of annual reports, quarterly reports, and various other reports published by the Ford Foundation between 1968 and 2000.
Photographs
- Publications - Working Files, 1973-2001; 1; 19.44 Cubic Feet 50 containers
  - Annual Report 1992 - Program-Related Investments (PRI)/Grants List, 1993 February (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Layout/Manuscripts/Proofs
  - Annual Report 1992 - Programs, 1993 January (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report 1992 - To Advance... Ford Foundation Description, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Bibliography, 1993 February-March (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Index, 1993 January-March (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Staff Listing, 1993 January-March (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Charts, 1993 February (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Map, 1993 February (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Board/Committees/Officers, 1993 January (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Inside Covers, 1993 March (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Urban Poverty/Grants List, 1993 February-March (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Rural Poverty/Grants List, 1993 February (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Governance and Public Policy/Grants List, 1993 February-March (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Education and Culture/Grants List, 1993 February (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Rights and Social Justice/Grants List, 1993 February (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report 1992 - International Affairs/Grants List, 1993 February-March (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Reproductive Health/Grants List, 1993 February-March (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report 1993 - Photos - Lists of Suggestions, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report 1993 - Typesetting Quotes, 1993 December-1994 January (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report 1993 - President's Review Reprint - Quotes, 1994 May (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report 1993 - Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Photo Log, 1994 December 13 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Photo Captions, 1995 February 8 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Memos (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Text, 1994 November-December (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Spring Report 1994 - Memos, 1994 April-May (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Photo and Licensing Agreements, 1994 October-December (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Susan V. Berresford Correspondence - Photos for 1994 Annual Report and Draft for Photo Licensing Agreement, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report 1994 - South African Wire Baskets (Annual Report Cover Photo), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Memos and Notes Regarding 1994 Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Photoshoot Innovations - Philippines (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report 1994 - Memo to Staff - Photographs, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Job #94-23 Works in Progress, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    The Ford Foundation's Neighborhood and Family Initiative reports
  - Job #94-06 Women in American Politics, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Job #94-20A 1994 Annual Report - General, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
    Includes final 1994 Annual Report
  - Job #94-20F 1994 Annual Report - Offprint, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Job #94-20E 1994 Annual Report - Representatives, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Job #94-20C 1994 Annual Report - Officers/Trustees, 1995 February-March (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Job #94-20D 1994 Annual Report - Letters to Congress, 1995 February-April (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Job #94-20B 1994 Annual Report - Bills, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 203)
  - Job #94-20B 1994 Annual Report - Bills, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 203A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - confidential material
  - Job #94-01 1994 Spring Report, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 204)
  - Job #94-01 1994 Spring Report, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 204A)
  - Job #94-13 Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 (Book), 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 205)
    Includes final copy of Innovations in State and Local Government 1994
  - Job #94-13 Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 (Book) (Box 21, Folder 205A)
  - Job #94-08 Investing for Social Gain Video Mailing (by Program-Related Investments), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    Includes Investing for Social Gain packet
  - Job #90-19 "The Male Role in Teenage Pregnancy", 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Includes final copies of The Male Role in Teenage Pregnancydistribution letters, and microfiche of materials sent to the ERIC system - Vera Institute of Justice, New York
  - Job # 95-23C Relinking Life and Work - Lists, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Job #23D Relinking Life and Work - Pegasus Licensing Agreement, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Job #95-23E Relinking Life and Work - Executive Tape Service, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Executive Tape Service - Newstrack Tape 1, 1996 October 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 9436)
    Ford Foundation Study Shows That Work and Family Can Be Successfully Integrated.
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Executive Tape Service - Newstrack Tape 2, 1996 November 19; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 9437)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Executive Tape Service - Newstrack Tape 3, 1997 January 7; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 9438)
  - Relinking Life and Work: Toward a Better Future: A Report to the Ford Foundation Based on a Collaborative Research Project with Three Corporations, 1996 November (Box 6, Folder 47)
    One copy of the publication
  - Job #95-23 Relinking Life and Work - General, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 48-50)
    Copyright information, reprint materials, correspondence, mailing list information, notes
  - Job #95-23B Relinking Life and Work - Bills, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 206)
  - Job #95-23B Relinking Life and Work - Bills, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 206A)
  - Job #95-19 Ford Foundation Work in Africa and Middle East, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Job #96-06 Ford Foundation in China, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    Includes final publication along with routing information and memo
  - Partnership for National Service - Project on Hold, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Job #96-20 Interim Document II, III, & IV - Replacing the Ford Foundation Current Interests, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Job #96-11 Interim Document I Replacing Current Interests of the Ford Foundation 1994 and 1995, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    Includes final copy of The Ford Foundation Report Summer/Fall 1996
  - Job #96-08 The Ford Foundation Resource and Reference Guide for Program Officers, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Job #96-02 1996 Summer/Fall Report - Bills, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 207)
  - Job #96-02 1996 Summer/Fall Report - Bills, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 207A)
  - Job #96-04 1997 Winter Report - Bills, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 208)
  - Job #96-04 1997 Winter Report - Bills, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 208A)
  - Job #96-03 1997 Winter Report - General, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Job #96-02 1996 Summer/Fall Report - General, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 58-59)
  - Job #96-01 1996 Spring Report - General (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Job #96-01 1996 Spring Report - Bills (Box 22, Folder 209)
  - Job #96-01 1996 Spring Report - Bills (Box 22, Folder 209A)
  - Job #97-01 1997 Spring Report - Bills, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 210)
  - Job #97-01 1997 Spring Report - Bills, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 210A)
  - Job #97-01 1997 Spring Report - General (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Job #97-02A 1997 Summer/Fall Report - General, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 62-63)
  - Job #97-02B 1997 Summer/Fall Report - Bills (Box 23, Folder 211)
    Restricted – Confidential material
  - Job #97-02B 1997 Summer/Fall Report - Bills (Box 23, Folder 211A)
  - Job #97-03C 1997 Ford Foundation Summer/Fall Report - Wirthlin Survey Project (Box 8, Folder 64-65)
  - Job #96-27 1996 President's Review, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Job #97-03 Winter Report - General, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Job #97-03 1998 Winter Report - Lists (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Job #97-03 1998 Winter Report - Polling (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Job #97-03 1998 Winter Report - Bills, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 212)
  - Job #97-03 1998 Winter Report - Bills, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 212A)
  - Winter Report 1988 - Questionnaire Results (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Job #97-04 Interim Document IV Replacing Current Interests, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Job #97-06A Innovations in American Government-Booklet, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 72, Box 10, Folder 73-74)
  - Job #97-06B Innovations in American Government - Bills (2 folders), 1997 (Box 23, Folder 213-214)
  - Job #97-06B Innovations in American Government - Bills, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 213A-214A)
  - Job #97-06C Innovations in American Government - Letters (Susan V. Berresford and Becky Cain), 1997 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Job #97-08 Booklet - Ford Foundation in the Philippines, undated (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Job #97-13B 1997 Annual Report - Bills, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 215-218)
  - Job #97-13B 1997 Annual Report - Bills, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 216A, 217A, 218A)
  - Job #97-13D 1997 Annual Report - Letters to Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Job #97-13F 1997 Annual Report - Offprint, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Job #97-13G 1997 Annual Report - Lists, 1998 April-June (Box 10, Folder 79, Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Job #97-16 Susan V. Berresford Speech: The Meaning of Globalization, University of North Carolina, 1997 September 29 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Job #97-17 Susan V. Berresford Speech: Donors Forum of Chicago, 1997 June 12 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Annual Report 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Annual Report 1973 - Estimates, 1973 October-1974 March (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Miscellaneous Information on Annual Reports, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Information - Estimates Etc. for 1978 Annual Report (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Annual Report 1978 - Offprints - Statement of Investments - Arts (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - 1981 Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 88-89)
  - 1987 Annual Report - Cover, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - 1987 Annual Report - Proofs, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - 1987 Annual Report - Type - Quotations, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - 1987 Annual Report - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - 1987 Annual Report - Quotations (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - 1987 Annual Report - Bills, 1987 December (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - 1986 Annual Report - Cover (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - 1986 Annual Report - Type Specifications, 1987 January 26 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - 1987 Annual Report Schedule, 1988 February (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - 1987 Annual Report - Layout Sheets, undated (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - 1987 Annual Report - Cover and Proofs, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - 1986 Annual Report - Covers, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 101-102)
  - 1988 Annual Report Photos - Rural Poverty, 1989 March (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - 1988 Annual Report Photos - Human Rights and Social Justice, 1988 August-September (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Urban Poverty Alternates - New York Times, 1988 July 21 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - 1988 Annual Report Photos - Education and Culture, 1989 March-April (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Photo Research, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Design and Design Agreement, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Correspondence, 1988 January-1989 May (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Specifications and Dummy Sheets, undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Grants List Revisions, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Type Quotations, 1989 April (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Typesetting Schedule, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Layouts and Covers, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - 1988 Annual Report: Staff Listing for Typesetting, 1989 May (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - 1988 Annual Report: Board of Trustees for Typesetting, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - 1988 Annual Report - Front Matter Typesetting (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Pablo Bartholomew, India Cultural Preservation, Photoshoot, Fall Report 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Pablo Bartholomew - Cultural Preservation India, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Winter Report 1994 - Photo Approval, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Winter Report 1995 - Proofs (Box 13, Folder 121, Box 14, Folder 130)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Photo Research - Photocopies and Description from the LA Times, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Photo Research - Human Rights, undated (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Photo Research - Urban Poverty, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Photo Research - Governance - Photocopies of Newspaper Articles, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Photo Research - Rural Poverty (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Photo Research - Education and Culture, undated (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - 1989 Annual Report Manuscript, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 128-129)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Photocopies of Unused Photographs, 1990 March (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Stock Photo Returns, 1990 February-April (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Schedule, 1990 January (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Manuscript, 1990 January-February (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Staff Announcements and Typographic Estimates, 1989 December-1990 January (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Cover Photographers, 1990 January (Box 20, Folder 201)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Specifications, 1990 January (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Photo Research (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - 1992 Annual Report - Idea File - Miscellaneous Photos, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Photo Suggestions - Newsletters and Clippings, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Photo Suggestions - Rural Poverty, 1993 May-August (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Photo Suggestions - Program-Related Investments, 1993 June-July (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Photo Suggestions/Text Draft - International Affairs, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Photo Suggestions/Text Draft - Media, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 143)
    Includes recommendations for Grant/FAP Action/Delegated-Authority Grants documents
  - 1993 Annual Report - Grants List - Latin America and Caribbean (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Drafts - Reproductive Health and Population, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Grants List - Rights, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Draft - Asia and Middle East, 1993 November (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Drafts - Investments, 1993 November (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Photo Suggestions - Governance and Public Policy (Box 16, Folder 149)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Draft - Rights and Social Justice (Box 16, Folder 150)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Draft - Governance and Public Policy (Box 16, Folder 151)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Draft, Photo Suggestions, Grants List - Urban Poverty, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 152)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Draft, Photo Suggestions, Grants List - Education and Culture, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 153)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Draft, Photo Suggestions - Media, 1993 October (Box 16, Folder 154)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Draft, Grants List - Rural Poverty, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 155)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Draft, Photo Suggestions - Program-Related Investments (Box 16, Folder 156)
  - The President's Review from The Annual Reports, 1979-1993 (Box 16, Folder 157-171)
  - The President's Review from The Annual Reports, 1979-1993 (Box 16, Folder 172)
  - President's Review from the Ford Foundation Annual Report 1993 - Proofs, 1994 May (Box 16, Folder 173)
  - President's Review Reprint, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 174)
  - President's Review - Reprint Quotes, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 175)
  - Pacific Century Premiere Invitation, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 176)
  - Catalog of Publications, Films, and Videos, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 177)
  - Catalog of Publications, Films, and Videos - Catalog Quotes, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 178)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Photo Research - Charts, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 179)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Memoranda and Manuscript Transmittal Forms, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 180)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 181)
    Photos have been removed but includes photo research and estimates
  - 1990 Annual Report - Photo Research and Grants List - Education and Culture, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 182)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Photo Research - Rural Poverty, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 183)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Photo Research - Urban Poverty, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 184)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Photo Research - Human Rights and Governance, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 185)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Photo Research, Education and Culture Draft, Program-Related Investments Draft, 1990 October (Box 18, Folder 186)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Photo Research - International Affairs, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 187)
  - Charts 1978-1992, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 188)
  - President's Review - Annual Report 1992, 1993 March (Box 18, Folder 189)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Urban Poverty Proofs, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 190)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Rural Poverty and Resources Proofs, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 191)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Governance and Publications Proofs, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 192)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Education and Culture Proofs, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 193)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Rights and Social Justice Proofs, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 194)
  - Annual Report 1992 - International Affairs Proofs, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 195)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Media Projects Proofs, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 196)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Program-Related Investments Proofs, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 197)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Reproductive Health and Population Proofs, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 198)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Financials Proofs, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 202)
  - Annual Report 1992 - General Type Specifications for Grants Lists, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 199)
  - Annual Report 1992 - Grants Specifications, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 200)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Financial Review, 1990 February-March (Box 28, Folder 279)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Index, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 280)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Human Rights and Social Justice, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 281)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Governance and Public Policy, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 282)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Education and Culture, 1990 March (Box 28, Folder 283)
  - 1989 Annual Report - International Affairs, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 284)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Population, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 285)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Program-Related Investments, 1990 February-March (Box 28, Folder 286)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Bibliography, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 287)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Cover, Back, Title Page, and Library of Congress Page, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 288)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Staff, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 289)
  - 1989 Annual Report - Urban Poverty, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 290)
  - 1990 Annual Report - Rural Poverty and Resources, 1990 February (Box 28, Folder 291)
  - 1993 Annual Report - Final Layout Sent to Printer (4 folders), 1994 March (Box 29, Folder 292-295)
  - Spring Report 1994 (5 folders), 1994 May (Box 30, Folder 296-300)
  - Summer Report 1994 (4 folders), 1994 July (Box 31, Folder 301-304)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Final Copy, 1994 November (Box 31, Folder 305)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Photo Approvals, 1994 October-November (Box 31, Folder 306)
  - Fall Report 1994 Proof with Corrections, undated (Box 32, Folder 307)
  - Fall Report 1994 Edits (3 folders), 1994 July-November (Box 32, Folder 308-310)
  - Fall Report 1994 Working Drafts, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 311)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Ad and Contents, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 312)
  - Special Report Intro, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 313)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Bracing for Change in Atecoxco By Lucy Conger, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 314)
  - Fall Report 1994 - No Going Back, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 315)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Equal Access to Justice, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 316)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Innovations in State and Local Government, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 317)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Taking a Closer Look at the News (Box 32, Folder 318)
  - Fall Report 1994 - When Welfare Ends, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 319)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Out of Cairo, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 320)
  - Fall Report 1994 - Briefly Noted, 1994 November (Box 32, Folder 321)
  - Fall 1994 - Recent Grants, 1994 October (Box 32, Folder 322)
  - Winter Report 1994 - Rural Chinese Women - Oona Sullivan, 1993 January-August (Box 32, Folder 323)
  - Winter Report 1994 - Empowering Education Program/American Social History (Box 33, Folder 324)
  - Winter Report 1994 - Michigan Upper Peninsular - Chris Reardon, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 325)
  - Winter Report 1994 - Schedule and Layout Memos, 1994 January (Box 33, Folder 326)
  - 2000 Annual Report (Box 33, Folder 327)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Assets (Including PRI), 2001 January (Box 33, Folder 328)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), 2001 January (Box 33, Folder 329)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - EMAC (Box 33, Folder 330)